Guide to the George A. Chauncey Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, Series V
  - Memory Book, 1960-1989 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Retirement certificate and tributes, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Resignation from PCUS centenary evangelism campaign and the response, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Retirement letters - 1, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Retirement letters - 2, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Audio-visual Material, Series VI
  - Photographs
    - Monticello years, 1954-1958 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - PCUS Atlanta years, 1958-1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Danville years, 1960-1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Richmond years, late 1960s - early 1970s (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Pre-GA Witness for Peace in DC, 1970s (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Central America negatives, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Central America, no date (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Audiotapes
    - Primarily sermons/talks by GAC, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Including: Radio Devotions at Danville, KY (May 1965); "Role of Pastor in Social Tension"(at UTS)(February 1967); Report of BCE staff at Clergy and Laity Concerned (CALC) mobilization, Washington DC (February 1967); Reflections on racial crisis at Church of Redeemer conference, Washington DC (May 1969);"The Frustration of Being a Christian Today" (address to Student Conference) (December 1967); "The Mission of Jesus – Lecture 3" (Synodical of GA)(1968)
    - Primarily sermons/talks by GAC, 1973-1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      Including: "Amnesty" (1973); "Debate on Coalitions" (1974);6 tapes related to homosexuality, including lecture, class discussion (1975);"Food policy" (1978)
    - Primarily sermons/talks by GAC, 1980-1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      Including: "National Concerns of Aging" (Montreat conference)(1980); Report on trip to El Salvador, Honduras, Nicaragua (November 1983);"What Is Our Responsibility?" (June 1984);National Impact Briefing on Issues Facing Congress (March 1987)2 tapes: GAC meeting with Presbyterian Laymen (March 1987);Prayer at Ortega visit (November 1987);"Work of WO, National Presbyterian Church" (February 1988);GAC / Leland Wilson debate (February 1988); Remarks to Warren Wilson seniors (December 1989)
    - Primarily sermons/talks by GAC, no date (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Including: "Global Situation"; "What is Justice?"